http://www.datapipe.com/information/legal/privacycenter

Cloud
Enable cloud adoption and transformation and optimize cloud strategies
Services
Cloud Adoption and Migration
Customized cloud migrations with an automation and cloud native focus
Cloud Management & Operations
Continuous infrastructure management, operations and enhancements
Cloud Optimization
Ongoing optimization to ensure the most cost-effective architecture
Technology
Multicloud
Reduced hybrid & multicloud platform complexity
Public Cloud
Migration, management and governance across leading cloud platforms
Applications
Deploy cloud native and SaaS solutions to increase efficiency and reliability
Services
Application Modernization
Eliminate technical debt with modernized application delivery
Internet of Things & Edge
Design, build, operate and manage IoT, edge devices and applications
Cloud Native
Deliver auto-scaling and hyper-resilient cloud native applications
CRM
Advisory, professional and managed services for CRM platforms
Digital Experience
Expertise for your customer experience application platforms
Data
Gain actionable insights with data management, engineering, intelligence, and powerful AI/ML toolkits
Services
Data Modernization
Streamline your data architecture across modern cloud data platforms
Analytics Platforms
Make confident decisions with modern data analytics platforms
Security
Evolve from monitoring to automating, preventing attacks while maintaining compliance
Cloud Native Security
Protect containers, microservices, serverless-based workloads
Application Security
Detect and mitigate vulnerabilities to protect critical apps
Cloud
Enable cloud adoption and transformation across leading cloud platforms
Industry Report
Rackspace Technology named a leader for the fourth consecutive year
Read More
Applications
Deploy cloud native and SaaS solutions across application platforms
Solve: Thought Leadership
What is the Key to Cloud Native Success? People and Process.
Read More
Data
Analyze and modernize your data across traditional and next-gen database platforms
Security
Compliance and security for your environment across cloud platforms
Cloud Native Security
Protect containers, microservices, serverless-based workloads
Industries
Our experts know your industry, and they know the challenges you’re facing. We deliver customized solutions to help solve these challenges every day.
Industry Report
Rackspace Technology named a leader for the fourth consecutive year
Read More
Insights
Latest Insights
Discover perspectives from industry experts around digital transformation and trends
Solve: Thought Leadership
To Build or to Buy?
Solve: Thought Leadership
Blogs
How Azure Data Services Help Your Business Innovate Faster and Smarter
Read Blog
Podcasts
From Chatbots to Alexa: The Evolution of Natural Language Processing
Listen Podcast
Customer Success
Hear what our customers have to say and find the support you need
Case Study
See how we helped McKesson reduce its dedicated data center footprint and centralize their IT operations,
See the Case Studies
Events & Publications
Stay up to date with the latest industry research, reports and events
Virtual Round Table
How Businesses are using AI and Machine Learning Today?
Watch Now
About
About Us
We advise, design, build and manage solutions across the multicloud, applications, data and security
Media Kit
Join the team!
Personal Information We Collect
Our Privacy Notice and specific privacy notices describe how we handle the personal information we collect about you. Personal information could include, for example, your name and contact details that you provide when you:
Purchase services from us
Apply for a job
Visit our websites
Sign up for our eventsDisclosure of Personal Information
When we need to provide your personal information to third parties, we will only share it to the extent reasonably necessary.
We may also share your personal information as required or permitted by law and as described in our Privacy Notice.
Rackspace Technology’s continued commitment to our contractual and legal obligations can be found in our Customer Data Processing Addendum.
Rackspace Technology is committed to protecting your data. Our contractual and legal obligations are flowed down to our processors and subprocessors.
Tracking Technologies
Rackspace Technology and our service providers or third party advertisers may use cookies, web beacons, or other similar technologies when you visit or interact with us online. For more information about our use of Tracking Technologies, please visit our Cookie Notice. If you wish to opt-out of interest-based advertising or other forms of “tracking” please refer to our cookie notice above.
Customers' Hosted Data
To find out more about customers’ hosted data and privacy go to our Customer Data Security and Privacy page.
If you receive hosting or other services from one of our customers and have privacy-related questions about those services, please contact our customer directly.
Access
If you would like to correct or update the information we hold about you, or revoke consent previously granted, please follow the instructions located in our Privacy Notice.
Intracompany Data Processing
As a global company, there may be times when Rackspace Technology may need to share personal data across its entities to support our customers and employees in the provision of services. The EU regulations on data protection (for example, the General Data Protection Regulation) require Rackspace Technology to have in place an appropriate method to legitimise cross border transfer of personal data. Rackspace Technology has put in place an Intracompany Data Processing Agreement to allow the processing of personal data among its entities.
To view a printer friendly version of our Privacy Notice, please click here.
Privacy Questions
If you have questions or complaints about our privacy statement or practices, please contact us at privacy@rackspace.com. If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact our U.S.-based third party dispute resolution provider (free of charge) at https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request.
Additional Privacy Notices
Mobile appsThis privacy notice explains our privacy practices when you use our mobile applications or interact with us through your mobile device.Job candidatesThis privacy notice explains our privacy practices when you apply for a job with us.CookiesThis privacy notice provides details on the cookies, web beacons and similar technologies used when you interact with us online. We also explain your options regarding these technologies.
Questions
If you have a privacy or data protection-related question about our services or the data that you host with us, please contact your Rackspace Technology support team or service delivery manager.
If your questions relate to our Privacy Statement, please email email us.
About
Support Portal
Careers
Investors
Contact Us
Consulting & Advisory Services
Multicloud Strategy
Data Modernization
×
You are using an outdated browser and are receiving a degraded experience. Please switch to the latest version of Microsoft Edge, Mozilla Firefox, Safari or Google Chrome.
[Dismiss]
